export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Choose your City',
        answers: ['Doomsville', 'Cash City', 'EzPz City'],
        correctAnswer: 'Paris',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Choose your job?',
        answers: ['Decide not to work at the moment and live off savings while exploring the city (+$0/month)',
            'Choose a job with a higher income but less stability (+$2,200/month)',
            'Go for a job with a very high income but significant instability (+$3,500/month)',
            'Opt for a job with a steady but low income (+$1,200/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [2,3,4,1],
        monthlyAdd: [0,2200,3500,1200],
        factor: "Risk Tolerance"
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Your job offers a few options for health insurance, Do you:',
        answers: ['Buy the insurance with the $25 deductible, $300 monthly payment and most comprehensive coverage (-$300/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $60 deductible, $200 monthly payment and above standard comprehensive coverage (-$200/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $120 deductible, $120 monthly payment and standard comprehensive coverage (-$120/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $200 deductible, $75 monthly payment and least comprehensive coverage (-$75/month : checking)'],
        correctAnswer: [4,3,2,1],
        monthlyAdd: [-300,-200,-120,-75],
        factor: "Risk Tolerance"
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Where would you like to live?',
        answers: ['City center (-$3000/month)',
                  'Midtown (-$2200/month)',
                  'Upstate (-$2500/month)',
                  'City limit (-$1800/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [0,0,0,0],
        monthlyAdd: [-3000,-2200,-2500,-1800],
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "You're a 20 minute drive from work. How would you like to commute?",
        answers: ['Buy a Car ($500/month)',
            'Take Public Transportation ($60/month)',
            'Lyft/Uber daily ($450/month)',
            'A mix of uber/walking/and public transportation ($120/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [3,4,1,2],
        monthlyAdd: [-500,-60,-450,-120],
        factor: "Planning"
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Choose Meals/Lifestyle',
        answers: ['Cook all meals at home with 3-4 takeout times a month ($350/month)',
            'Cook meals at home but eat out 1-2 a week ($400/month)',
            'Mostly eat out while cooking 1-2 a week ($500/month)',
            'Get all meals through takeout and cook 3-4 times a month ($600/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [4,3,2,1],
        monthlyAdd: [-350,-400,-500,-600],
        factor: "Spending Habits"
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Choose your job?',
        answers: ['Decide not to work at the moment and live off savings while exploring the city (+$0/month)',
            'Choose a job with a higher income but less stability (+$2,900/month)',
            'Go for a job with a very high income but significant instability (+$5,500/month)',
            'Opt for a job with a steady but low income (+$1,500/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [2,3,4,1],
        monthlyAdd: [0,2900,5500,1500],
        factor: "Risk Tolerance"
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Your job offers a few options for health insurance, Do you:',
        answers: ['Buy the insurance with the $70 deductible, $400 monthly payment and most comprehensive coverage (-$400/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $170 deductible, $300 monthly payment and above standard comprehensive coverage (-$300/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $220 deductible, $220 monthly payment and standard comprehensive coverage (-$220/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $300 deductible, $175 monthly payment and least comprehensive coverage (-$175/month : checking)'],
        correctAnswer: [4,3,2,1],
        monthlyAdd: [-400,-300,-220,-175],
        factor: "Risk Tolerance"
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Where would you like to live?',
        answers: ['City center (-$4500/month)',
                  'Midtown (-$2400/month)',
                  'Upstate (-$3700/month)',
                  'City limit (-$1600/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [0,0,0,0],
        monthlyAdd: [-4500,-2400,-3700,-1600],
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: "You're a 20 minute drive from work. How would you like to commute?",
        answers: ['Buy a Car ($700/month)',
            'Take Public Transportation ($80/month)',
            'Lyft/Uber daily ($600/month)',
            'A mix of uber/walking/and public transportation ($160/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [3,4,1,2],
        monthlyAdd: [-700,-80,-600,-160],
        factor: "Planning"
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Choose Meals/Lifestyle',
        answers: ['Cook all meals at home with 3-4 takeout times a month ($450/month)',
            'Cook meals at home but eat out 1-2 a week ($500/month)',
            'Mostly eat out while cooking 1-2 a week ($600/month)',
            'Get all meals through takeout and cook 3-4 times a month ($700/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [4,3,2,1],
        monthlyAdd: [-450,-500,-600,-700],
        factor: "Spending Habits"
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: 'Choose your job?',
        answers: ['Decide not to work at the moment and live off savings while exploring the city (+$0/month)',
            'Choose a job with a higher income but less stability (+$1,500/month)',
            'Go for a job with a very high income but significant instability (+$2,500/month)',
            'Opt for a job with a steady but low income (+$900/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [2,3,4,1],
        monthlyAdd: [0,1500,2500,900],
        factor: "Risk Tolerance"
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: 'Your job offers a few options for health insurance, Do you:',
        answers: ['Buy the insurance with the $25 deductible, $250 monthly payment and most comprehensive coverage (-$300/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $70 deductible, $150 monthly payment and above standard comprehensive coverage (-$200/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $160 deductible, $70 monthly payment and standard comprehensive coverage (-$120/month : checking)',
            'Buy the insurance with the $300 deductible, $50 monthly payment and least comprehensive coverage (-$50/month : checking)'],
        correctAnswer: [4,3,2,1],
        monthlyAdd: [-300,-200,-120,-50],
        factor: "Risk Tolerance"
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: 'Where would you like to live?',
        answers: ['City center (-$1900/month)',
                  'Midtown (-$1100/month)',
                  'Upstate (-$1400/month)',
                  'City limit (-$800/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [0,0,0,0],
        monthlyAdd: [-1900,-1100,-1400,-800],
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: "You're a 20 minute drive from work. How would you like to commute?",
        answers: ['Buy a Car ($350/month)',
            'Take Public Transportation ($30/month)',
            'Lyft/Uber daily ($200/month)',
            'A mix of uber/walking/and public transportation ($60/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [3,4,1,2],
        monthlyAdd: [-350,-30,-200,-60],
        factor: "Planning"
      },
      {
        id: 16,
        question: 'Choose Meals/Lifestyle',
        answers: ['Cook all meals at home with 3-4 takeout times a month ($250/month)',
            'Cook meals at home but eat out 1-2 a week ($300/month)',
            'Mostly eat out while cooking 1-2 a week ($400/month)',
            'Get all meals through takeout and cook 3-4 times a month ($500/month)'],
        correctAnswer: [4,3,2,1],
        monthlyAdd: [-250,-300,-400,-500],
        factor: "Spending Habits"
      },
    ],
  };
  